<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Beckenham Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Beckenham Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Not for ourselves alone</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Welcome to Beckenham</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_events">Events</string>
    <string name="menu_celebrities">Famous Residents</string>
    <string name="menu_history">Historical sites</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_accommodation">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="menu_entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="menu_transport">Transport</string>
    <string name="menu_restaurant">Restaurants and Cafes</string>

    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="place">Place</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>

    <string name="welcome_header">Welcome to \nBeckenham Tour Guide App!</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Since its early development from a small village to town Beckenham
        has its motto NON NOBIS SOLUM written on its coat of arms. In English: NOT FOR OURSELVES ALONE.\n\n
        And Beckenham has always been true to this motto. Unfortunately less so in 2019.
        The Council where Beckenham belongs, does exactly the opposite. As it stands,
        it is the only council in London (!) which has refused to take in 50 children refugees.\n\n
        Come and explore wonderful things in and around Beckenham.</string>

    <string name="profile_header_text">Sirus Laia</string>
    <string name="profile_body_text">Quite late to learn coding, but I have been always interested in IT.\n\n
        So when I hadn\'t started my official Android programming course, I was running a project
        I called the Nias Keyboard Project. Basically coding for Android before learning how to code :)\n\n
        I have a few apps ideas so I\'m looking forward to finishing the course and starting real work!\n\n
        My Background\n\n
        I was born in Nias Island, the biggest of all islands off West Sumatra, but I left the island,
        when I started my high school years in Sibolga, Sumatra. Then after finishing
        my philosophical study in Pematang Siantar, I went to Münster, Germany,
        where I studied and worked for almost 11 years.\n\n
        I came back to the island just 3 weeks before 2004 tsunami hit Indian ocean, including Nias Island,
        and 3 months before the earthquake finally devastated the island. As programme manager and
        deputy director I got the task of organising the relief, rehabilitation and reconstruction work,
        while building up a humanitarian and social organisation called Caritas Sibolga.\n\n
        After 4 years work in Caritas Sibolga I started a new job in administration in Sibolga.
        But Padang earthquake of 30 Sept 2009 took me back to NGO world. I moved to Padang, West Sumatera,
        to be programme manager of the Caritas joint emergency response for Karina KWI (Caritas Indonesia).\n\n
        In April 2010 I made myself free for a new way of life and then moved to Europe
        (or came back to :) ) as I had always wanted to call Europe my home.</string>

    <string name="attribution">Photo above: the strange statue without name outside the St Mark\'s Square, Bromley.
        All photographs by creator of the app. Other images are either from respective source (bromley.gov.uk,
        wikipedia.org where mentioned or organisers of events) or pixabay.com.</string>

</resources>
